ADAPTED FROM DEMON KING
OF JINJIANG LITERATURE CITY
ORIGINAL WORK BY JIULU FEIXIANG
- What are you doing?
- Come with me!
Little Immortal Criminal.
Chang…
Lord Changheng.
Lord Changheng, don't kill me.
How bold.
You escaped from prison.
You should be executed
according to the law.
Changheng…
Orchid.
You know that the criminal is with you,
but you didn't report it.
And you hid him in Arbiter Hall!
I…
Stop.
I'm very disappointed in you.
No!
This is
the feeling of fear.
It has been so long since I felt this.
Good thing it was a dream.
Wake up.
Let me sleep for another 7.5 minutes.
It's already 5 a.m.
I want to sleep more.
Get up quickly and fix the Destiny Book.
Leave me alone!
If you feel bored in the morning,
go to the greenhouse
and count all my flowers.
Let me sleep in peace, all right?
I have no time to waste with you.
Now…
One.
Two.
Three.
What's going on?
What black magic
did this Little Flower Spirit do?
If you feel bored in the morning,
go to the greenhouse
and count all my flowers.
Let me sleep in peace, all right?
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Shangque.
Shangque!
My lord, what can I do for you?
Fifteen.
Sixteen.
Seventeen.
My lord, are you…
counting flowers?
Why are you doing this?
I'm meditating
to recuperate my vitality.
You're indeed my lord.
Your cultivation
has reached the state of perfection,
but you still won't slack off.
Under your rule,
you can revive Cangyan Sea
and unify the three realms
in no time.
I remember that the Xilan Tribe
recorded all the secrets
in the Xilan Book.
The method of deciphering
the Xilan Holy Seal should be in it.
Do you know where the Xilan Book is now?
I know.
The Xilan Book was in Yunmeng Lake
back then
and our tribe found it.
Now it is heavily guarded
in the secret cabinet of our tribe.
In the past 30,000 years, I--
Then get it now.
Hurry!
Yes.
Eighty…
Eighty-eight.
My lord. The Xilan Book is here.
My lord!
I see.
Since the One Heart Curse is given,
I will share the same joy, sorrow, death,
and injury with the curse caster.
Our bodies and minds
will be connected as one person.
No matter what I do,
she will not be affected.
But I will feel
whatever she feels.
If someone wants to kill me,
they can just kill her.
That means…
She is my biggest weakness now.
Once the curse caster gives a command
with the Xilan Holy Seal,
I can't disobey it.
How cruel.
Am I going to be controlled
by this plant
from now on?
My lord.
My lord, please calm down.
Based on my observation,
even if this Xilan Curse
is strange and despicable,
Little Flower Spirit doesn't seem to know
that she's from the Xilan Tribe.
Even if she accidentally cast the curse,
she doesn't know how to use it.
Forget it.
After she fixes the Destiny Book,
I will be able to find
the reincarnation spirit of Lady Chidi,
unlock 100,000 demon soldiers,
and destroy the Fairy Realm.
It's just a Xilan Curse.
I'll be able to break it by then.
Yes.
I'm so sleepy.
Little Immortal Criminal.
Why are you here?
8,452.
What?
Your greenhouse
has 8,452 flowers.
You…
You really counted
the flowers in the greenhouse?
Yes.
Is it because of what I said?
I just said it casually.
How could you take it seriously?
Why are you so naive?
Remember.
Every word you say
is very important to me.
You can't say things casually from now on.
Well,
I'm just an ordinary plant.
No one takes my words seriously.
Since my master left to go traveling,
no one cared about me.
So you don't have to…
Forget it.
Very good.
Go and fix the Destiny Book.
Fix the Destiny Book?
What does it matter to him
whether I fix the Destiny Book or not?
He's not my master.
Why is he telling me what to do?
He must want to have a conversation.
It's rare to have some free time.
I won't do it.
I'm hungry. I'm going to have breakfast.
Breakfast?
Do you still want to eat breakfast?
Don't you know
that it's already nine o'clock?
You don't cultivate
and do what you need to.
You wake up so late every day
and you want to pass
the immortal examination?
What do you know?
If I don't sleep well,
how can I have energy?
Sleeping is the first priority
for those who cultivate.
In the three realms,
I have never seen
a lazy woman like you.
You…
See?
Am I not right?
How can you have strength
if you don't eat?
Eating is the first priority
for people who cultivate too.
Is it good?
The food outside
is better than the ones here.
It is better
to have freedom in the right way.
Am I right?
By the way,
we've known each other for so long.
I still don't know who you are
and what your name is.
My name
is Dongfang…
Qing…
Did I catch a cold in Haishi yesterday?
What did you say your name was?
Dongfang Qiang?
Don't be upset
if I say this.
The surname Dongfang is the same
as the deceased Dongfang Qingcang.
It's not good.
The deceased Dongfang Qingcang?
Yes. Don't you know?
Do you not even know
the Battle of Two Tribes?
Haven't you ever read books?
What's important
is to fix the Destiny Book.
Forget it.
I won't argue with this lazy
and ignorant Little Flower Spirit.
Daqiang, I'm not talking nonsense.
Dongfang Qingcang
is really evil.
The Fairy Realm suffered a lot
from him back then.
So the word "Dongfang"
is very unlucky and ominous
in the entire Yujing.
No, in the entire Shuiyuntian.
Is that so?
Don't be sad.
Your surname is from your parents.
You can't choose it.
You're already very lucky.
At least you have a surname.
I'm just an orchid.
I have no parents
and no surname.
Do you not have a name?
Everyone calls me Orchid.
Although you are unlucky
to have the same surname
as Dongfang Qingcang,
you look much more handsome than him.
You
are short-sighted
and only around 1,000 years old.
Have you really met the strongest
in the three realms,
the great Moon Supreme Dongfang Qingcang?
I've never seen him.
But it's written in the books.
Dongfang Qingcang
has a green face and fangs.
His long hair drags on the floor
and his hair is full of lice.
I heard he never brushed his teeth
and bathed for thousands of years.
He has bad breath.
He was so disgusting.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't talk about these
disgusting things while you're eating.
What I want to say
is that you are much better than him.
Do I have to thank you?
There's no need.
If you really remember my kindness,
go back
to where you should be.
That's better than anything.
Since you know the Moon Supreme so well,
do you know what he likes to eat?
What Dongfang Qingcang likes to eat most
are fair and chubby little fairies
with thin skin and tender meat like you.
He ate 10,000 or 8,000 fairies.
Boiled,
roasted,
fried, steamed,
and
raw.
"Thirty thousand years ago,
the Battle of Two Tribes
was extremely tragic.
The God of War, Lady Chidi,
had unparalleled valiance.
She did her best to seal
100,000 demon soldiers with her death.
Inspired by the heroic and fearless spirit
of the God of War,
the immortals
fought against the enemy bravely!
Dongfang Qingcang was utterly defeated,
beaten black and blue,
kneeling and begging for mercy!"
Enough!
What are you doing, Daqiang?
"Beaten black and blue,
kneeling and begging for mercy"?
Is that what's in the history books
of Shuiyuntian?
Are you struggling with this?
Of course the books don't say that much.
Distorting historical facts.
No wonder you can't even pass
a minor immortal examination.
What do you know?
There's only a little bit
of boring stuff in the history books.
If I want to pass
the immortal examination,
I have to use these figures of speech
to describe the intense situation vividly
at that time.
Did you
make up all these details?
Yes.
I made it up.
How is it? Isn't it vivid?
Why is a little plant
reading about fighting all day long?
Read something else.
Right.
Soon, the festival is coming.
I'll listen to you.
I'll read something without fighting.
This festival celebrates
the Fairy Tribe's victory
in the Battle of Two Tribes.
Shuiyuntian celebrates
the victory of the battle
and the sealing of Moon Supreme
on that day.
What are you doing?
You scared me.
Daqiang.
You don't have to use that much strength
to make festival pastries.
Festival?
Pastries?
Yes.
It's all right if you don't know
how to make it. I'll teach you.
Take your time. Look.
Pound the glutinous rice
very hard like this.
Pound it hard like this
to make a paste.
Then we can make pastry later.
Look.
See?
Be careful.
Watch out.
It's hot!
Why is it so hot?
Don't grab it with your hands from now on.
You can't even think of a way
not to get burned.
You're stupid indeed.
What do you know?
The next step is the important one.
It really looks like him.
Like what?
Dongfang Qingcang.
Look, he has a green face and fangs,
showing his teeth and claws.
It's so funny.
Right. This one.
This is the Shuofeng Sword
of the God of War, Lady Chidi.
Thrust it into Dongfang Qingcang here.
Then keep twisting it.
Stop!
I mean,
you're wrong.
Lady Chidi killed herself
with Shuofeng Sword.
You don't have to be so mean.
Isn't it enough
for the meaning and plot to be similar?
How can it just be similar?
Lady Chidi never really defeated
Dongfang Qingcang.
Fine.
Whatever you say.
By the way,
didn't you say that you don't know
what the Battle of Two Tribes is?
How do you know these trivial details?
These are not trivial details.
Forget it.
When you went to get your stuff just now,
I had already read all the books there.
I saw the torn portrait
in the book too.
Who is that?
Why are you nervous?
I'm not.
I…
You… I…
I just feel so hot.
By the way, I haven't had time
to sun my master's liquor yet.
I have to go sun the liquor.
Little Flower Spirit.
How much longer are you going
to put off fixing the Destiny Book?
My lord, are you all right?
I've wasted the whole day
with Little Flower Spirit.
Fixing the Destiny Book
is postponed until tomorrow.
My lord, please calm down.
The Destiny Book of Lady Chidi's
primordial spirit is in your hands now.
It's in the bag.
There is no need to rush.
Little Flower Spirit
doesn't know the power of the Xilan Curse,
yet she controlled me like a fool.
If she knew,
wouldn't I really become her servant then?
In the three realms,
I don't believe
there is no way to break the Xilan Curse.
- Shangque.
- Yes.
Go get the Heart-Hiding Hairpin.
You must be careful
not to be noticed.
I will surely do my best.
Once I break the curse,
I will kill Little Flower Spirit.
Wait.
Prepare some water. I want to take a bath.
Yes.
What?
The Arbiter Hall
has not been so lively for a long time.
Although Daqiang
always loses his temper,
isn't that bright,
and always refers to himself so highly,
I don't think he is bad.
Although his power is stronger than mine,
it's not a big deal.
He probably did not make a big mistake.
It's pitiful that he has been
in the Haotian Tower
for so long.
Now,
he's able to live freely.
You've been resting for so long.
Why can't you fix it yet?
Why are you staring at me?
If you stare at me like this,
how can I focus?
I won't watch you. Just fix it.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm good at fixing Destiny Books.
But this Destiny Book is too bad.
I've never fixed
such a broken Destiny Book before.
It's a bit hard.
Hey.
My lord,
Little Flower Spirit's power
is badly consumed.
Maybe it's because she almost touched
the seal in Haotian Tower
and consumed her power.
Now,
we're forcing her to fix the Destiny Book.
That's why she fainted.
In her current condition,
when will she be able to fix it?
My lord.
A Destiny Book is formed by
the spiritual energy of heaven and earth.
It contains the karma of everything.
- If we want to fix it, first, we must--
- What do you want to say?
Before she fully recovers,
I'm afraid there is no way to fix it.
When will she fully recover then?
One day?
Two days?
Do you want me
to wait for ten days or a half month?
My lord,
I only know a little
about Chinese medicine.
Little Flower Spirit is from Xilan Tribe.
She must have a special physique.
All I know is that she needs
to have a good rest now.
As to when she will fully recover,
I don't know.
Forget about ten days or a half month…
Say it.
It might take 3, 5, or 100 years.
That is
a possibility.
My lord,
even if you have great power,
you can't keep spending it like this.
I know what to do.
Go back to your work.
You don't have to stay with me.
My lord.
I don't understand.
Who is this Immortal Pill made for?
What medicine
is worth all your effort?
What he's guarding isn't a pill,
but his sincerity.
Sincerity?
A few thousand-year-old child shouldn't
ask about things he shouldn't know.
My lord, you can't guard this forever.
How about I guard it for you?
Don't worry.
I won't fail you.
Qingchuan,
it's rare for me to visit the Fairy Realm.
Why don't we find a place
to have some tea?
Tell me
about the interesting things
in Yujing recently.
- But--
- Let's go.
Lord Ronghao, let go of me!
I want to stay with my lord.
FIVE HUNDRED YEARS AGO
You're awake.
Don't get up.
You're badly injured.
You can't move.
Unfortunately, my power is weak.
I can only help you
stop the bleeding first.
Thank you, fairy.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Actually, I'm not considered a fairy yet.
I just transformed into a human form.
I don't even have a name.
Do you have a name?
Don't you know me?
I don't know anyone
except my master.
I don't have any friends either.
Lord Changheng!
I'll surely pass the immortal examination.
I will definitely enter
the Fountain Palace!
My lord, you can't do this.
Disturbing the natural law and karma
might destroy your body and spirit.
Disturb the natural law?
Haven't I disturbed
a lot of natural laws already?
My lord.
Only Arbiter can pry
into a Destiny Book's secret.
It's hard to find her now.
The success and failure
still depend on Arbiter's disciple,
Little Flower Spirit.
But I'm finding a way
to break the Xilan Curse now,
so I can't stay in Shuiyuntian for long.
I'm afraid
you can only
look after her yourself.
Forget it.
It shouldn't be hard
to take care of a plant.
"Xilan Plant
was born in the secret realm of Xilan.
It likes warmth
and dislikes severe cold weather.
It likes a place with partial shade
and dislikes sun exposure.
It likes the first rays of sunshine
from the east in the morning.
Except during the Spring Equinox,
Tomb-Sweeping Day, and Grain Rain,
you can't move its roots."
"If it's dry and lacks water,
the roots will shrink and dry out
and the leaves will be burned and curled.
Then it will develop badly
and its spiritual wisdom
will be hard to open.
Xilan Plant is very pure.
If its spirit develops,
it needs to be watered
with rootless water.
The best time of the day
is from 5:00 a.m. to 7:00 a.m.
Avoid overwatering
to prevent waterlogging,
resulting in rotten roots and leaves."
What is rootless water?
Saliva?
Sweat?
Tears?
"Heavenly water is rootless
and born from the morning dew."
It's morning dew.
How ridiculous!
Do I have to catch it for her
drop by drop?
No way.
My lord.
But the Destiny Book--
If it weren't for the Destiny Book
and the One Heart Curse,
I would have killed her long ago.
She wants me to serve her?
No way.
How strange.
Daqiang.
Where did this idiot come from?
Run!
The look in his eyes is so fierce!
Daqiang.
How long do I have to wait?
Once I break the curse,
I'll kill the damn Little Flower Spirit,
burn the greenhouse,
destroy the Shuiyuntian,
break the bones of Lord Yunzhong,
and soak them in liquor.
ARBITER HALL
My lord!
I finally found you.
Lord Yunzhong is summoning you
for a meeting at Yunzhong Water Pavilion.
I'll go later.
But
Lord Yunzhong especially instructed
that you hurry and not delay.
Daqiang.
ARBITER HALL
Where is he?
He's usually always around.
Where exactly did he go?
Could he have left?
That's great.
He's gone!
Creeper, Succulents, Holly, Peach.
Stop hiding.
He's really gone.
Come out.
If you don't come out,
I will take your spirit stones.